<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Content on Marcin Misiak on GitHub Pages</title>
    <link>https://zq-psk.github.io/ssg/docs/hugo/articles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Content on Marcin Misiak on GitHub Pages</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zq-psk.github.io/ssg/docs/hugo/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding articles</title>
      <link>https://zq-psk.github.io/ssg/docs/hugo/articles/add/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zq-psk.github.io/ssg/docs/hugo/articles/add/</guid>
      <description>Adding articles  In the project folder, open the content folder.
By default, the folder is content. The &amp;ldquo;book&amp;rdquo; theme uses the content/docs folder. Create a new Markdown file in the location where you want to add an article.
For more information on content organization, read this article. Open the new file with a text editor. At the beginning of the file, add the following metadata:  title (string) weight (integer) description (string) optional: other metadata that your site uses    Example:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content enrichment</title>
      <link>https://zq-psk.github.io/ssg/docs/hugo/articles/enrich/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zq-psk.github.io/ssg/docs/hugo/articles/enrich/</guid>
      <description>Content enrichment You can enrich your content by using shortcodes or inserting HTML into the Markdown file.
Shortcodes Hugo offers a number of built-in shortcodes. Themes usually add additional shortcodes you can use. You can also create your own.
Shortcodes are processed when the Markdown sources are parsed into HTML.
A full list of the built-in shortcodes is available in the Hugo documentation.
The shortcodes added by a theme are usually described in the theme&amp;rsquo;s README.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviewing the output</title>
      <link>https://zq-psk.github.io/ssg/docs/hugo/articles/review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zq-psk.github.io/ssg/docs/hugo/articles/review/</guid>
      <description>Reviewing the output Before publishing your site to GitHub Pages, you should review the output locally. GitHub Pages do not provide an on-line staging environment and the static site pushed to &amp;ldquo;origin/master&amp;rdquo; is published immediately.
Hosting the preview  Open the Terminal by pressing CTRL + ALT + T. Navigate to the project folder. Enter hugo server.
Result: The site is hosted locally on your system.
By default, the site is available at http://localhost:1313/.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>