<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo on Marcin Misiak - writing samples</title>
    <link>https://zq-psk.github.io/ssg/docs/hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hugo on Marcin Misiak - writing samples</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zq-psk.github.io/ssg/docs/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>https://zq-psk.github.io/ssg/docs/hugo/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zq-psk.github.io/ssg/docs/hugo/install/</guid>
      <description>Hugo Installation Hugo offers a few installation methods. A complete list is available in the Hugo documentation.
Installing Hugo on Ubuntu This method requires the most manual work, but it gives you strict control over the installed version. This is beneficial if you want to update Hugo at your own pace, giving yourself time to resolve any issues caused by the introduction of features that break backwards compatibility.
 Go to the Hugo releases page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initializing a site</title>
      <link>https://zq-psk.github.io/ssg/docs/hugo/initialize/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zq-psk.github.io/ssg/docs/hugo/initialize/</guid>
      <description>Initializing a site Before you can add styling and content to a site, you must initialize a folder structure and configuration files.
 In the file explorer, create a folder for your project.
NOTE: Whenever this page mentions project folder, it refers to this folder. Open the Terminal by pressing CTRL + ALT + T. Navigate to the project folder by using the cd command.
Example  marcin@marcin-HP:~$ cd Documents/gitRepositories/myHugoSite  Enter hugo new site .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Themes</title>
      <link>https://zq-psk.github.io/ssg/docs/hugo/themes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zq-psk.github.io/ssg/docs/hugo/themes/</guid>
      <description>Themes To give your website a graphical layout, you must add a theme.
You can also create your own theme from scratch. This requires knowledge of HTML, CSS, JS, and Hugo templating.
Adding a theme This procedure explains how to download a theme and use it without connection to the theme&amp;rsquo;s original repository. This allows you to easily introduce your own modifications or update the theme at your own pace.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>