<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marcin Misiak - writing samples</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Marcin Misiak - writing samples</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo</title>
      <link>/docs/hugo/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/hugo/hugo/</guid>
      <description>Hugo Static Site Generator Installing Hugo on Ubuntu Hugo offers a few installation methods. The method described in this procedure lets you control the version you are installing and installs it globally.
 Go to the Hugo releases page. Choose a release :  If you are preparing to create a new site, choose the latest release. If you are going to work with an existing site, on the list locate the same release that the site is deployed with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing for GitHub Pages deployment</title>
      <link>/docs/deploy/prep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/deploy/prep/</guid>
      <description>Configuring Hugo for GitHub Pages deployment  In the root folder of your repository, open the config.toml file. In the configuration file, search for the publishDir setting. Perform one of the following actions:  If the setting exists, change its value to &amp;quot;docs&amp;quot; If the setting does not exist, create it by adding the following line to the file: publishDir = &amp;quot;docs&amp;quot;   Change the value of baseURL to the URL of your page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying the site</title>
      <link>/docs/deploy/deploy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/deploy/deploy/</guid>
      <description>Site deployment Building the site Prerequisites Check out the &amp;ldquo;master&amp;rdquo; branch.
Procedure  Open the Terminal by pressing CTRL + SHIFT + T. Navigate to the root folder of the repository. Enter hugo
Result: The static site is built in the docs directory. In the file explorer, open the docs directory. Double click index.html.
Result: The site opens in the browser. Verify that the content was generated properly. Commit the changes in the docs directory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VSC</title>
      <link>/docs/vscodium/vsc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/vscodium/vsc/</guid>
      <description>VS Codium Installing VS Codium on Ubuntu  Open the Ubuntu Software application.
By default, the application is available from the application bar on the left side of the screen. In the upper-left corner of the application window, click the search icon. In the search field that opens, enter VS Codium In the results, click VS Codium. In the application details that open, click Install. In the pop-up that opens, enter your user password and press ENTER.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>